24小时
第三季  第24集
前情提要
艾伦·米利肯的药瓶上查出有雪莉的指纹
Alan Milliken's prescription bottle turned up with Sherry's fingerprints on it.
我可以找福克斯顿
I can call Foxton.
他能摆平这一切
He can make this all disappear.
你只要点头就行了
All you have to do is give me the ok.
大卫指使你来的 是吗?
David put you up to this,didn't he?
雪莉 我...
Sherry,I...
警方认为是我杀了艾伦
The police think I killed Alan.
哦 我告诉过你闭上嘴的
Well,I told you to keep your mouth shut.
你自作自受
It's nobody's fault but your own.
哦 天啊 雪莉
Oh,my God. Sherry.
不
No.
你犯了叛国罪
You committed treason.
你帮助一个
You facilitated the escape of a man
杀了瑞恩·查佩尔和近千平民的凶手逃之夭夭
who is responsible for the death of Ryan Chappelle and almost a thousand civilians.
运气好的话 最少也得判20年
With luck,the best you can hope for is 20 years.
告诉我怎么找到那些运输人 斯蒂芬
Tell me how to find your couriers,Stephen.
否则我就把她送进去
Or I am going to put her in that building.
你不会的 她和这件事毫无关系
You wouldn't dare. She has nothing to do with this
那些已经死了的民众也与此无关
Neither do the people in those body bags.
等你女儿染上病毒
When your daughter is infected,
我会让你亲眼看着她死去
I am going to make you watch her die.
爸爸 让他们住手
Dad,stop them.
斯蒂芬 你没多少时间了
Stephen,you are out of time.
住手 住手 停下来 我全告诉你
Stop,stop,stop,I will tell you.
第11瓶病毒在哪?
Where's the 11th vial?
洛杉矶
Los Angels.
袭击目标是什么?
What's the target?
选择一个能够尽可能
His instruction were to select a public place
造成最大伤亡的公共场所
where maximum casualties would be inflicted.
目标停止移动了
The target has stopped moving.
目标停下来了
The target has stopped.
把包放下
Drop the bag.
立刻趴在地上 不许动
Get on the ground,now. Don't move.
-怎么回事?  -它在哪儿?
-What's going on?  -Where is it?
什么在哪?
Where's what?
-它在哪儿?  -什么在哪?
-Where is it?  -Where's what?
蔡斯
Chase.
你们在干什么 这是怎么回事?
What are you guys doing,what's going on?
有信号反应
I have got the signal.
你们在找什么?
What are you looking for?
只是个发信器
It's just a transmitter.
他把这个放在一个无关的人身上 他不是拉本斯
He's put it on an innocent. This man is not Rabens.
立刻关闭车站
Shut the station down now.
以下事件发生于下午12:00到下午1:00之间
The following takes place between 12:00 pm and 1:00 pm.
我是德斯勒
This is Dessler.
米歇尔 我是杰克
Michelle,it's Jack.
我们刚让拉本斯跑了
We just lost Rabens.
他把定位器放到一个路人身上
He dumped the GPS beacon onto an innocent.
这么说病毒还在他手上?
Which means he still has the virus?
目前看来是的 他应该还没跑远
We have to assume so. He couldn't have gotten very far.
我们正在搜查车站
We are sweeping the station now.
我们已经关闭了整个车站
We have locked down the entire building.
我们会让所有乘客通过检查点的全身扫描
We are gonna start moving passengers through monitored checkpoints.
那你打算怎么找出拉本斯?
How will you find Rabens?
我们还没有他的拼图
We still don't have a sketch on him.
我们需要桑德斯来辨认
We need Saunders to make an I.D.
我要你把他从关押点送到克萝伊那里
I want you to move him over from holding to Chloe's station.
我们正在安装实时传送设备 几分钟就好
We are sending up a live feed,you should have it in a few minutes.
好 我这边会准备好的
Ok,we will be ready on our end.
米歇尔 盖尔·奥尔特加的妻子特丽萨来了
Michelle,Gael Ortega's wife Theresa is here.
好的 杰西 让她进来
All right,Jesse,send her in.
根据克萝伊的口供
According to Chloe's statement,
你们一直都想捉拿桑德斯
you were working in parallel to bring down Saunders,
即使在你被他胁迫的情况下
even while you were complying with his demands.
对 是的
Yeah,that's right.
我 我把自己和桑德斯的通话录音给了克萝伊
I,I gave Chloe a recording of a conversation between Saunders and myself.
克萝伊还说你故意在录音上做了手脚以拖延她的进度
Chloe also said you intentionally scrambled the voice to slow down her progress.
托尼 你是不是把米歇尔的生命安全置于公众和国家安全之上 ?
Tony,did you put Michelle's life ahead of public safety or national security?
是 我承认
Yes,I did.
他们说他感染了病毒
They said he was exposed to a virus.
对 是的
Yeah,that's right.
他死的痛苦吗?
Did he suffer?
不 没有 他去的很快
No,no,he went quickly.
盖尔.
Gael
他是个英雄
He was a hero.
他竭力想阻止病毒的释放
He tried to stop the virus from being released,
即使病毒瓶爆炸的时候 他也没有退却
and when it was,he just kept working.
一直到最后
Till the end.
谢谢
Thank you.
我能带走他的遗物吗?
Can I pick up his things?
当然
Of course.
我去看看能帮上你什么
I will go see what I can do.
好
Ok.
在这等我
Wait here.
金.
Kim
是 米歇尔
Yes,Michelle.
那位是奥尔特加夫人 盖尔的妻子
That's Mrs. Ortega. Gael's wife.
你带她去盖尔的位子
I need you to take her to his station,
整理他的私人物品然后带走
pick up his personal belongings.
好的
Sure.
谢谢
Thank you.
让他坐下
Sit him down.
喂
Hello.
金 我需要你的帮助
Kim,I need you.
桑德斯来辨认拉本斯了
Saunders is here to I.D. Rabens.
抱歉 我正陪着奥尔特加夫人
Well,I am with Mrs. Ortega.
米歇尔说我可以调用任何来帮我
Michelle said I could reassign anyone I wanted to help me,
现在我需要你 别让我说第二遍
and I want you,so please don't make me ask again.
嗯 好吧 我让巴里陪着她吧
Ah,fine. I will get Barry to watch her.
巴里
Barry.
是
Yeah.
你帮奥尔特加夫人收拾一下盖尔的物品
Please watch Mrs. Ortega while she gathers Gael's things.
好的
Sure.
请自便
Take as much time as you need.
谢谢
Thanks.
不好意思 巴里
Excuse me,Barry.
能签个字吗?
Can I get a signature?
哦 好的
Oh,sure.
谢谢
Thanks.
还有什么事吗?
Anything else?
不 没有了
No,that's it.
先生 你能上前一步排好队吗?
Sir. If you will just step up to the line?
就在这
Right here.
请抬起头 先生
Chin up,please,sir.
把头抬起来
Chin up.
2A放大点
Move in closer on 2A.
喂 杰克 是我
Yeah,Jack,it's me.
有认出来吗 米歇尔?
Any matches,Michelle?
不 还没有
No,nothing yet.
-进展怎么样?  -4C
-How far have you got?  -4C.
目前 两组照片只辨认完一组
So far,we have gone through the 1st 2 sets of photos.
下一组正在上传 保持联系
Next group is uploading now. Stand by.
不是他
It's not him.
这页上有吗?
Is there anything on this page?
3B 放大一点
3B,closer up.
不 不是他
No. That's not him.
不是
No.
3号工作站 找到匹配对象了吗?
Station 3,do we have a match?
还没 杰克
It's a negative,Jack.
没看见他
I don't see him anywhere.
把头抬起来 先生
Head up,sir.
放大5B看看
Bring up 5B.
不 不是 不在这一页
No,he's not,he's not here.
好的 下一页
All right,bring up the next page.
-这个呢?  -也不是?
-What about this one?  -No?
他杀了我丈夫
He killed my husband.
是他杀了盖尔
He killed Gael.
米歇尔 你那边出什么事了?
Michelle,what's going on over there?
桑德斯遭到枪击
Saunders has been shot.
你说什么?!
What are you talking about?!
谁开枪打他?
Who shot him?
盖尔的妻子
Gael's wife.
你等等 杰克 快叫医生来
Hold on,Jack. I need medical here now.
米歇尔 他情况怎么样了?
Michelle,what is his condition?
很危险
Looks critical.
无论如何都要保住他的命
You do everything you can to keep him alive.
他是抓到拉本斯的唯一线索
He's our only connection to Rabens.
蔡斯
Chase.
在
Yeah.
杰克
Jack.
说
Talk to me.
他死了
He didn't make it.
该死的
Son of a bitch.
我会再联络你
We will get back to you.
桑德斯刚刚遭到枪击
Saunders has just been shot.
他死了
He's dead.
别动 女士 别动
Don't move,madam,don't move.
他杀了盖尔
He killed Gael.
根据我们从运输病毒的人
Between the information we've gotten
和其他方面所掌握的情报来看
from the captured couriers and our own intelligence,
我们可以确认
We've been able to confirm that
桑德斯是这次行动的唯一策划者
Saunders was the sole architect of today's actions.
如果我们能抓到这最后一个人
If we catch this last man.
亚瑟·拉本斯
Arthur Rabens.
危机就将解除
that'll be the end of the threat.
如果抓不到 我们就将回到起点
And if not,we are back to square one.
而病毒会还会重新出现
And the virus is back on the market.
找到他
Find him.
-你好 韦恩  -约瑟夫 能让我们单独谈一会吗?
-Hello,Wayne.  -Joseph,could you give us a minute?
-谢谢 约瑟夫  -不用谢
-Thank you,Joseph.  -Mr. President.
韦恩 你从雪莉家找到药瓶了吗?
Wayne,did you get the prescription bottle from Sherry's house?
找到了
Yeah.
嗯 太好了
Well,that's good.
大卫...
David...
今晚发生了一件很可怕的事 其实我不...
Something horrible happened and I don't...
雪莉死了
Sherry is dead.
什么?
What?
怎么会死的?
How?
朱莉娅 她闯了进来 然后她...
Julia,she came in and she...
她枪杀了雪莉 然后开枪自尽
She killed her,and then she turned the gun on herself.
她们都死了?
They are both dead?
是的
Yeah.
听着 我不会假装我们能
Listen,I am not going to try to pretend that
当这事没发生一样
we can just put this behind us,
但事实是...
but the fact is...
事实是我们彻底从这场政治游戏中解脱了
The fact is that politically,we are free of everything.
包括米利肯的勒索 他的死亡
Free of Milliken's extortion,his death.
包括雪莉的搅局
free of Sherry's involvement.
你觉得这仅仅是一场政治游戏?
You are thinking of the politics of this?
我孩子的母亲刚刚被人谋杀
The mother of my children has just been murdered.
我曾经深爱的女人刚刚在我面前自杀
And the woman that I love just killed herself in front of me.
我明白你现在的感受
I just understand how you feel.
但我们可以编个故事 大卫
But there's a story here,David.
编个故事来掩盖这一切
There's a story that can tie this all together.
艾伦·米利肯与雪莉有染
Alan Milliken was having an affair with Sherry.
朱莉娅发觉了之后 把他们两个都杀了
Julia found out,and then she killed them both.
不 不 不 我不想听
No,no,no,I don't want to hear it.
-你的情感阻碍了...  -够了!
-Your emotions are clouding...  -No!
大卫 求你了 听我的吧
David,please,just listen to me.
让我一个人静静
Leave me alone.
大卫 求你了!
David,please!
珍妮
Jeanie.
什么事 总统先生?
Yes,Mr. President?
帮我接通和我子女的可视通话
Would you get my son and my daughter on a conference line.
我们需要把旅客按十人一组分开
We are going to separate the crowd into units of 10.
每一组都要派警员看守
I want an officer assigned to each unit.
每个警员要保证组里没有人
That officer's gonna be responsible to make sure that
能在没有我或者是反恐局其他探员允许的情况下来离开
no one leaves that unit unless authorized by me or another CTU agent.
明白
I understand.
同时要自己搜查每一个旅客
We are also going to search every passenger.
仔细检查每个手提箱 钱包和口袋
and I mean every briefcase,purse and pocket.
并且要核对他们的身份
And we are gonna verify their identification.
那恐怕要一整天时间
We will be here all day.
-一旦找到他就可以了  -是 长官
-Not if we find him.  -Yes,sir.
我要你再次对车站进行搜索
I want you to initiate another search of the station,
包括一英里之内的各个方向的隧道
including the tracks,a mile in each direction.
-辛苦了  -遵命
-Thank you.  -Yes sir.
杰克
Jack.
都搞定了
We are locked down.
每个出口都有两名警卫把守
We got 2 men at every exit.
很好
Good.
我们现在还能做些什么?
Is there anything else we can do right now?
没有 在确认拉本斯身份之前暂时没有
No,not until we get an I.D. on Rabens.
杰克 我有话对你说
Jack,listen,
关于墨西哥的事...
about Mexico...
我知道你都是为了工作
I hope you know I understand you were just doing your job.
听着 我也花了很长时间才明白
Look,it took me a long time to understand that
要想做好这份工作
if you want to do this job well,
你必须无牵无挂...
you have to stay detached...
如果你能接受 就没问题
If you can accept that,you will be fine.
是啊
Yeah.
我已经接受了
Well,I have accepted it.
所以我在想 今天之后我就不干了
That's why I am thinking after today,I am done.
我不想和她们分开 杰克
I don't want to be detached,Jack.
我不能没有金 也不能没有我女儿
Not from Kim,not from my daughter.
我准备转去做文职
I am going to request a transfer to the floor.
你决定好了吗?
You sure about this?
一样是为国效力
I'd still be serving my country,
而且还可以照顾我多关心的人
and take care of the people I care about.
我亏欠她们太多了 杰克
I owe them that,Jack.
金怎么说?
What did Kim say?
她说只要我不做外勤人员就可以考虑和我继续交往
I think she's willing to give it a try as long as I am not in Field Ops.
你怎么想 杰克?
What do you think,Jack?
我的意见对你来说是最无关紧要的
I am the last person you should be asking.
这是你和金之间的事
This is between you and Kim.
无论你作出什么样的选择 我都会支持的
Whatever you choose,I would support.
你是好样的 蔡斯
You are a good man,Chase.
过来 过来 排成一条队伍 先生们
Let's go,let's go. Moving in,form a line here,sir.
请你们快一点 我们会检查你们随身携带的财物和证件
Please,fast,we'll be checking your belongings and your identification.
你这组只有九个人
You only have 9 people in your unit,
穿棕色夹克的那个人呢?
where is the man in the brown jacket?
我没注意
I don't know.
蔡斯 有个旅客下落不明
Chase,we have a passenger unaccounted for.
我是杰克·鲍尔 有两个弟兄倒在西北出口
This is Jack Bauer,we have 2 LAPD officers down at the northwest exit.
马上在街角给我准备一辆车
I need transportation to meet me on the corner.
我是联邦探员
I am a federal agent.
你们知道这发生了什么吗?
Did you see what happened here?
有人劫车
A carjacking.
-看到车牌号了吗?  -没有
-Get a make on the car?  -No.
我是杰克·鲍尔 霍普大街和第七大道之间有人死亡
This is Jack Bauer,we have got a civilian casualty on Hope and Seventh.
你看到车往哪个方向去了吗?
Did you see which way the car went?
是 是的 往那个方向去了
Yeah,yeah,he went straight down there.
马上派车过来
I need that transportation now.
米歇尔 我是杰克
Michelle,this is Jack.
拉本斯逃出了地铁站
Rabens is out of the station.
重复 拉本斯逃脱了
I repeat,Rabens is out.
他往第五大道往东行驶了不超过五分钟
He was headed east on 5th street less than 5 minutes ago.
我需要确认一辆被抢车辆
I need to I.D. a stolen car.
请给我在车管局的数据库里查找车主名叫...
I want you to get me a DMV readout on a...
-弗兰克·卡萨尔  -... 弗兰克·卡萨尔
-Frank Kassar.  -... A Frank Kassar.
请在方圆五英里之内设立路障
Then I want you to set up roadblocks in a 5 mile radius.
采用卫星监控 交通录像等所有手段找到他
and coordinate SAT surveillance,traffic cameras,everything we have got.
喂
Yeah.
弗莱德 是我 我想和你谈谈
Fred,it's me. I need to talk to you now.
好 我马上来
All right. I will be right out.
我要出去一下
I need to step out.
布拉德·拉本斯逃脱了
Brad,Rabens is gone.
他从交通运输管理局的地铁站里逃出来了
He got through the perimeter at the MTA station.
怎么搞的?
How the hell did that happen?
不管怎么搞的 事情已经发生了
It doesn't matter how it happened,it happened.
我们已经确认他劫持了一辆淡蓝色的雪弗兰迈锐宝
We identified the vehicle he carjacked as a light blue Malibu.
我们设立了路障 调用了交通监控摄像和卫星监控系统
We set up a roadblock and uplinked traffic cams and satellite sweeps.
但我需要托尼来协助行动中的数据交换
But I need Tony to coordinate the data flow with tactical.
这没什么可担心的 布拉德
There's no downside here,Brad.
你知道他是不会逃跑的 而且他的参与对行动有很大帮助
You know he's not a flight risk and he'd be a major asset to the operation.
我把托尼放出去可能会被指控的
I could be brought up on charges if I let Tony out.
我们不能跟丢拉本斯
We can't lose Rabens.
除非你愿意亲自指挥调度...
So unless you want to take responsibility and run tactical yourself...
你这是在浪费时间 布拉德
You are wasting time,Brad
跟我去指挥中心
We need you on the floor.
快点 克萝伊 拉本斯在哪?
Come on,Chloe,where's Rabens?
再等一会 杰克
Just a second,Jack.
我想我找到了
I think I have got a match.
一辆淡绿色的雪弗兰迈锐宝 在第五大道范欧文区
A light green Malibu,intersection of Fifth and Vanowen.
好的 我们离那不远
Ok,we are only a few blocks away,
我们马上赶过去
we are gonna head over there now.
亚当 给我一个牌照的放大图片
Adam,get me a closer shot of that plate.
马上就好
Doing it now.
我回来了 杰克 米歇尔都跟我说了
I am back in play,Jack,Michelle got me up to speed.
托尼 还要多久能得到牌照号?
Tony,how long till the plate's I.D?
亚当 确认是那辆吗?
Adam,do we have a match?
是的 是他 完全吻合
Yes,it's him. It's pretty match.
杰克 是他
Jack,it's him.
他正朝哪个方向行驶?
Which direction is he headed?
往东面的德尔马去了 刚过了弗兰克林大街
East on Del Mar,just past Franklin.
就是这区了
It's this block.
就是那辆
Right there,right there.
托尼 发现他了 他正在曼宁大街向南开往查塔姆中心
Tony,we got him. He's headed south on Manning toward the Chatham Center.
请求支援
We are going to need backup.
收到
Copy that.
托尼 支援会从哪边过来?
Tony,where's that backup coming in from?
他们会从东面和南边包抄他
From the east and from the south on a reciprocal course.
那就没错了 我们正在迪索托大街向西行驶
Ok,we just made a right. We are headed west on De Soto.
快把那车挪开
Get that thing out of here now.
托尼 我们跟丢了
Tony,we have been cut off.
他向北往朗代尔去了
He made a right on to Lawndale. He's headed north.
我们和他相距大约三个街区
We are about 3 blocks behind him.
是的 杰克 我们在这个区域有三辆车堵截他 就在拐弯处
Yeah,Jack,we have 3 vehicles in the area ready to cut him off. At the corner.
杰克 我们在帕姆街西北的张伯伦截住他了
Jack,we got him pinned on Chamberlain,just north of Palm.
堵住他 我还差两个街区就到了
Keep him there. We are 2 blocks away.
他逃进了张伯伦的一所中学 从大门进去的
He's running into the middle school on Chamberlain,main entrance.
托尼 我们马上就到这所中学了
Tony,we are coming up on the middle school now.
托尼 他进了学校 一会儿和你联系
Tony,he's in the school. Gotta get back to you.
告诉后面赶来的人守住各个出入口
Tell the arriving teams to secure the exits.
我们不能疏散学校里的人
We can't evacuate this school.
否则他就有机会跑掉 我们行动
We run the risk of losing him. Let's move.
海耶斯 守住西面的门
Hayes,cover the west exit.
-有发现吗?  -没有
-You got anything?  -Nothing.
守好这个门 谁也不许离开
Cover your exit. No one leaves this building.
蔡斯 带你的人去搜查礼堂
Chase,take your men and search the auditorium.
所有师生请留在你们的教室里并锁上门
All teachers and students are instructed to remain in their classrooms and lock their doors.
我重复 留在教室里并锁上门
I repeat: remain in the classrooms and lock the doors.
没事的 孩子们
It's all right,children.
蔡斯 我是杰克 二楼安全 收到了吗?
Chase,it's Jack. Second floor is clear. Do you copy?
蔡斯?
Chase?
不 蔡斯 不要动 不会有事的
No,Chase,just lay still. Everything's going to be all right.
这是我阻止他携带病毒逃跑的唯一办法
This is the only thing I could do to keep him from escaping with the virus.
别浪费时间了 拿不下来的
Don't waste your time,it's not coming off.
你说什么?
What are you talking about?
拉本斯根本没有打算把它拿下来
Rabens didn't even try to remove it.
如果能打开的话 他早就开了
If he could unlock it,he would have.
托尼 拉本斯死了
Tony,Rabens is dead.
病毒在我们手里
The virus is in our possession.
但这个装置的释放程序已经启动
But the dispersal device has been activated.
好的 杰克 我需要你找到一个安全的容器
All right,Jack,I need you to find a secure container.
任何密封的装置
Anything airtight.
什么?
What?
稍后再解释给你听
I will explain later.
现在我需要联系上
Right now I need you to put me in touch with one of the teams.
拆除过这种装置的小队之一
that's been able to disarm the device already.
好 马上打给你
All right,I will get back to you.
要快
Hurry.
小心那个装置
Just support the device.
杰克 我不知道最后会变成什么样
Jack,I don't know how this is all going to turn out,
但我想让你替我和金说声抱歉
but I want you to tell Kim that I am sorry.
你来告诉金 你亲口和她去说
You got to tell Kim,you tell her yourself.
我们会没事的
We're going to get through this.
坚持住 会没事的
You just stay with me. We are going to get through this.
-杰克 我帮你接通了  -好
-Jack,I am patching you through.  -OK.
我是罗杰·萨莫斯
Roger Summers here.
罗杰 我的搭档把病毒释放装置扣在了自己手腕上
Roger,my partner had to fasten the dispersal device to his wrist.
以阻止罪犯携带它潜逃
to stop the courier from escaping with it.
我需要知道如何停止它的定时装置或是卸下它的扣锁装置
I need to figure out how to disarm the timer or remove the clamp.
不可能的 它的扣锁装置是钛合金制造的
Forget about the clamp. It's titanium,
同时里面还有防损坏装置
and it's also wired into the tamper proof mechanism.
那好 那我们来停止定时装置 我该怎么做?
Fine,then let's disarm the timer. What do I do?
在扣锁装置反面有个金属板
There's a plate at the opposite end of the clamp.
你把它打开
You need to open that up.
好 我看到了
Ok,I see it.
蔡斯 坚持住 坚持住
Chase,stay with me. Stay with me.
好 我看到定时装置了 3分51秒 正在倒计时
Ok,I have got the timer. 3 minutes,51 seconds,counting down.
好了
Ok,done.
好 最左端的线应该是红色的
Ok,the furthest to the left should be red.
小心剪断它 不要碰到其他线路
Cut it without making contact with the others.
你准备好了吗?
You ready?
我剪断了 但是计时器仍在倒计时
I cut the red wire,but the timer is still counting down.
没事的 再剪一条它就会停下的
That's ok. The timer will stop with the next cut.
找到绿色的线 在右边的一组线中
Locate the green wire. It's in the group to the right.
罗杰 我没找到绿线
Roger,I don't have a green wire.
你看到有什么颜色的线?
What color wires do you have?
橙色 黄色 黑色和紫色
Orange,yellow,black and purple.
杰克 这个装置不一样
Jack,the devices don't match.
别慌张 在我们这边想到办法之前不要再剪任何线了
Don't panic,and don't cut any more wires until we can figure this out on our end.
快点 我们的时间越来越少了
Hurry. We are running out of time.
杰克 你走吧
Jack,you need to go.
你不走 我哪也不去
I am not going anywhere without you.
来吧
Do it.
-他们会再打来的   -你必须这么做
-They are going to call back.  -You have to.
他们会再打来的
They are going to call back.
没事的
It's ok.
我是杰克·鲍尔
This is Jack Bauer.
大楼三楼北侧科学实验室有我们的人受伤
We have a man down on the 3rd floor science lab northeast corner of the building.
请求医疗救护
requiring medical assistance.
万分紧急 快
Emergency,now.
能让我们单独谈谈吗?
Could you give us a minute,please?
怎么了?
What's going on?
我会被继续监禁
I am back in custody.
哈蒙德会带我去联邦法庭
Hammond's taking me down to Federal.
不 不 他们不能这么做
No,no,they can't do this.
你今天做了很多事 他们不能这样
Not after everything you have accomplished today.
米歇尔 我置你的幸福在国家安全之上
Michelle,I put your well being above the country's.
没有什么人或事可以改变这一事实
Nothing anybody can say will ever change that fact.
不 他们可以
Yes,they can.
-托尼 别这么说 我...  -米歇尔
-Tony,don't talk like this. I...  -Michelle.
我做不到 我不会放弃你的
I can't,I won't give up on you.
米歇尔 拜托 求你了米歇尔 别这样
Michelle,come on. Please,Michelle,don't do this.
宝贝 你还活着
Baby,you are alive.
而且没有人因为我所做的事而受到伤害
And nobody else got hurt because of what I did.
这已经比我希望的强多了
And that's more than I hoped for.
我可以接受这样的结果
I can live with that.
就算是进监狱
Even in prison.
托尼 是时候了
Tony,it's time.
-我是鲍尔  -鲍尔探员 请稍等一下总统
-This is Bauer.  -Agent Bauer,please hold for the President.
杰克
Jack.
总统先生
Mr. President.
我想亲口跟你道声谢
I wanted to thank you personally.
不光是因为你今天所做的事
Not only for what you have done today,
而是为你所做的一切
but for everything.
这个国家又一次欠了你的情
This country continues to owe you a great debt of gratitude.
谢谢 长官
Thank you,sir.
今天在这么短时间我给了你一个艰难的任务
I put you in an unimaginable position earlier today,
我让你结束自己一位同事生命
when I asked you to take the life of one of your colleagues.
请原谅我的行为
Please forgive me for that.
总统先生 这没什么可原谅的
Mr. President,there is nothing to forgive.
这是必须的
It's what had to be done.
这不是今天唯一的牺牲
It wasn't the only sacrifice made today.
我明白
I understand.
埃德蒙兹探员怎么样?
How's agent Edmunds doing?
他正在手术中
He's in surgery now.
可能还要过几天才能知道
It's going to be a few days before we know
他的手是否能复原
whether or not he can use his hand.
好吧 等他好一点 能说话的时候
Well,when he's strong enough to talk,
我想亲自感谢他
I'd like to thank him personally.
他会很敢接的 总统先生
He would appreciate that,sir.
你知道吗 杰克 像你这样的人
You know,Jack,men and women like you,
你的勇气和献生精神让我自惭形秽
your courage and level of commitment humbles me.
谢谢你 总统先生
Thank you,Mr. President.
我会告诉反恐局的每一个人 您对他们的工作非常满意
I will let everyone know at CTU that you appreciated the job they did
杰克 还有件事
Jack,there's one more thing,
请你在公开之前不要对任何人提起
and please don't discuss this with anyone until it becomes public.
但我想私下里亲口告诉你
But I wanted you to hear it from me,personally.
我决定不再寻求连任
I have decided not to seek reelection.
这将是我唯一的任期
This will be my only term.
总统先生 请允许我说两句
Mr. President,I hope you don't mind me saying so,
我认为你做了一个错误的决定
but I think you're making a mistake.
好了 不管对错 我已经决定了
Well,mistake or not,it's what I have decided.
作为一个普通的公民 我希望能和你成为好朋友
When I am a private citizen,I hope we can become better friends.
我将深感荣幸 先生
That would be an honor,sir.
谢谢你 杰克
Thank you,Jack.
谢谢你 总统先生
Thank you,Mr. President.
进来
Come.
总统先生 一切准备就绪
Mr. President,the motorcade's ready.
谢谢你 埃里克
Thank you,Eric.
谢谢你 韦恩
Thank you,Wayne.
-爸爸  -嘿
-Dad.  -Hey.
蔡斯会没事吧?
Is Chase going to be ok?
医生说情况很乐观
The doctors are very optimistic.
他们及时给他进行了手术
They got him into surgery very quickly.
哦 谢天谢地
Oh,thank God.
太好了
Come here.
我听说你和蔡斯决定做些改变
I hear you and Chase are going to make some changes.
我真替你感到高兴
I am very happy for you.
我原以为你会为此不开心
I thought you were going to be upset about it.
我为你感到自豪
I am so proud of you.
我想你不论你作出什么决定都是正确的
I am sure whatever choices you make will be the right ones.
谢谢你 爸爸
Thank you,Dad.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你没事吧?
You going to be ok?
是的 我没事
Yeah,I am going to be fine.
有些事我必须去克服
There's something I have to deal with.
但我会没事的
But I am going to be fine.
你打算在这等蔡斯从手术室里出来?
You are going to wait here for Chase to get out of surgery?
是的
Yeah.
我离开一会 马上回来
I've gotta leave for a little while,but I will be back.
好
Ok.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你 爸爸
I love you,too,Dad.
杰克 你在吗?
Jack,you there?
杰克?
Jack?
我是杰克
This is Jack.
刚接到管区通知
I just got a call from District.
他们要审问桑德斯那些运输病毒的同伙
They have started interrogating Saunders' courier.
需要你的帮助
We could use your help.
-杰克?  -是
-Jack?  -Yeah.
杰克 听到了吗?
Jack,did you copy?
马上赶到
I am on my way.